(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-06T17:49:56.047606",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
こんばんわー！ カウントナイトTVです！
Good evening! This is Count Night TV!
この番組は、姫森ナイトであるポルナイトと、ふぶるナイトが司会でお送りする音楽ランキング番組です。
Presented by Pol-Night and Fuburu-Night, this music countdown show...
今日のハッシュタグは、こちら！ #姫森ルナ生誕アニソンLIVE で拡散してね！
Today's hashtag is right here! Spread the word with #HimemoriLunaBirthdayAnisonLIVE!
さてさて、本日のランキングテーマは姫森ルナおすすめアニソン特集TOP10とのことですが、
Now then, today's ranking theme is Himemori Luna's recommended anison special TOP 10,
どんな曲がランクインしているんでしょうね！
I wonder what kind of songs made the ranking!
それではまずは、10位から8位まで見ていきましょう！
Well then, let's first take a look from 10th to 8th place!
カウントナイト！
Count Night!
侵略! 侵略! 侵略! 侵略! 侵略! 侵略! イカ娘!
Invasion! Invasion! Invasion! Invasion! Invasion! Invasion! Squid Girl!
キラキラな海と風 輝くアトリウム
Sparkling sea and wind, a shining atrium.
みんなで集まって はじめましょ はじめましょ
Let's all gather together, let's begin, let's begin!
ホラホラそこのキミ、我儘(わがまま)な態度で
Hey hey, you over there, with that selfish attitude,
おちたりタタクしたり イカンでしょ イカンでしょ
dropping or tapping things, that's no good, that's no good!
ほんとはもっと優しい気持ちを 持ってるでしょう あなたも
You actually have much kinder feelings inside too, don't you?
ひとりぼっちも 海の平和も
The lonely ones and the peace of the sea—
イチゲン キゲンも 幸せも 守ります!
I'll protect everyone's moods and happiness too!
イーカンジウムテキに☆ススメ
Moving forward at an invincibly awesome pace!
東の島行ったら おおっぱいっぱい 大勝利!
If we go to the eastern island, big jackpot, a sweeping victory!
東の島行ったら お宝いっぱい 大勝利！
Head to the eastern island for treasure and a huge victory!
イーカンジボボ方にススメ
Advancing in a great squid-ward direction!
イーカンジムチュウにススメ
Advancing completely absorbed!
誕生石うれしい このまま天下を取れないか？
My birthstone makes me happy, can I take over the world like this?
侵略 攻略 計画 成功! 侵略 攻略 計画 成功
Invasion, conquest, plan, success! Invasion, conquest, plan, success!
侵略 攻略 イカ娘チュー!
Invasion, conquest, Squid Girl!
侵略!侵略!侵略!侵略! 侵略!侵略!侵略!侵略! 侵略!侵略!侵略!侵略! 侵略!侵略! イカ娘!
Invasion! Invasion! Invasion! Invasion! ...Squid Girl!
ウキウキな海の風 駆け出すプロムナード
A cheerful ocean breeze, running out onto the promenade.
あなたを見つけたら 並びましょ 並びましょ
Once I find you, let's walk side by side.
ドキドキ気にしてる 始まりの5分前
My heart races anxiously, five minutes before it starts.
オシタリ遅れたりは イカんでしょ イカんでしょ
Being late or lagging behind is out of the question!
ホンネはいつもかくしていたよ キズつかないようにね
I've always hidden my true feelings so I wouldn't get hurt.
ヒキコモリでも 平和主義でも
Whether a shut-in or a pacifist,
いばらの道でも 幸せをつかみたい!
even on a thorny path, I want to grasp happiness!
イーカンジモテキにススメ
Advancing in a great, invincible direction!
イーカンジムジャキにススメ
Advancing in a mischievous, great way!
アミとスミをかけたら 効果抜群 ハイタッチ!
Toss a net and ink, super effective, high five!
イーカンジボボ方にススメ
Advancing in a great squid-ward direction!
イーカンジムチュウにススメ
Advancing completely absorbed!
目指すどこかが合ったら 合体仕様にならないか？
If our destinations align, how about combining into one?
侵略 攻略 計画 成功! 侵略 攻略 計画 成功
Invasion, conquest, plan, success! Invasion, conquest, plan, success!
侵略 攻略 イカ娘チュー!
Invasion, conquest, Squid Girl!
今の世の中はちょっとキュウクツな感じ
Today's world feels a little cramped,
だけど僕達は今日も 好きなものだけは変わらないまま大人になるよ
but we'll grow up today too, keeping the things we love unchanged.
娘まじ人類！私が生きてるこのクソッタレな地上を侵略してやるぜ！
Seriously, humanity! I'll invade this damn surface where I live!
イーカンジモテキにススメ
Advancing in a great, invincible direction!
イーカンジムジャキにススメ
Advancing in a mischievous, great way!
2人でホラ いったら 思い出たくさんできました
Look, going together, we made so many memories!
イーカンジボボ方にススメ
Advancing in a great squid-ward direction!
イーカンジムチュウにススメ
Advancing completely absorbed!
ひとりじゃ ねえ サミシイ このまま一緒に行かないか?
Being alone is lonely, won't you come along with me?
侵略 攻略 計画 成功! 侵略 攻略 計画 成功
Invasion, conquest, plan, success! Invasion, conquest, plan, success!
侵略 攻略 計画 成功! 侵略 攻略 イカ娘チュー!
Invasion, conquest, plan, success! Invasion, conquest, Squid Girl!
潔く カッコ良く 生きて行こう…
Let's live purely and coolly...
たとえ2人離ればなれになっても… Take my revolution
Even if the two of us drift apart... Take my revolution
光差す校庭 手をとり合い 誓い合った なぐさめ合った
In the sunlit schoolyard, holding hands, swearing and comforting each other,
もう恋は二度としないよって
saying we'd never fall in love again.
そんな強い結束は カタチ変え
That strong bond changes its form,
今じゃこんなにたくましい 私達の Life style, everyday...everytime
now so resilient, our lifestyle, everyday...everytime.
頬を寄せあって
Pressing our cheeks together,
うつる写真の笑顔に 少しの淋しさつめ込んで
packing a little bit of loneliness into the smiling photos.
潔く カッコ良く 明日からは 誰もが振り向く女になる
Purely and coolly, starting tomorrow, I'll become a woman everyone turns to look at.
たとえ2人離ればなれになっても 心はずっと一緒に
Even if the two of us drift apart, our hearts will always be together.
愛はお金では買えないって
They say love can't be bought with money...
知っているけど
Even though I know...
“I”でお金は買えるの？
Can you buy love with money?
T.V.で言ってた
That's what they said on TV.
無感動…無関心きりがないね
Apathy... indifference, it never ends.
若い子みんなそうだと思われるのは
Assuming all young people are like that
feel so bad! どうしようもないじゃない
feels so bad! There's nothing we can do.
でもね私達
But you know, we
トモダチの事 何より大切にしてる
hold our friends dearer than anything else.
きっと大人よりも
Surely more than adults do.
夢を見て 涙して 傷ついても
Dreaming, weeping, and getting hurt,
現実ちはがむしゃらに来るし
reality comes at us recklessly anyway.
自分の居場所 存在価値は失えない
I can't lose my place or my worth.
自分を守るために
To protect myself.
I'll go my way 戻れないそれぞれの道を選ぶ時が来る前に
I'll go my way before choosing separate paths.
こんなにも こんなにも 大切な想い出 とき放つよ
I'll unleash these precious memories, so dear.
Take my revolution 生きて行こう
Take my revolution, let's live on.
現実はがむしゃらに来るし
Reality comes at us recklessly,
自分の居場所 存在価値を見つけたい
but I want to find my place and my worth.
今日までの自分を
The self up until today,
潔く 脱ぎ捨てる 裸になる
I will cleanly strip away and become bare.
自由を舞う 薔薇のように
Like a rose dancing in freedom,
たとえ2人離ればなれになっても
even if the two of us drift apart,
私は世界を変える
I will change the world.
眠れない夜は
Sleepless nights
君のせいだよ
are all because of you.
さっき別れたばかりなのに
Even though we just parted ways a moment ago,
耳たぶが for you 燃えている for you
my earlobes are burning for you.
やった やったよ
Yay, yay!
初めてのチュウ 君とチュウ
My first kiss, a kiss with you.
I will give you all my love
なぜか優しい気持ちが ああいっぱい
My heart is so full of gentle feelings.
初めてのチュウ 君とチュウ
My first kiss, a kiss with you.
I will give you all my love
涙が出ちゃう男のくせに
Even though you're a guy, you start crying—
Be in love with you
デートコースはもう決めたんだ
I've already decided on our date course.
明日の夢がふくらんでくる
Tomorrow's dreams are swelling up inside.
この愛を to you いつまでも to you
This love is for you, always for you.
きっと きっと きっとさ
Surely, surely, surely...
ohh
はじめてのチュウ
First kiss
君とチュウ
You and chu
I will give you all my love
なぜか優しい気持ちが
For some reason, a gentle feeling
あー いっぱい
Ah, so full
はじめてのチュウ
First kiss
君とチュウ
You and chu
I will give you all my love
涙が出ちゃう男のくせに
Even though I'm a man who sheds tears
be in love with you
はじめてのチュウ
First kiss
君とチュウ
You and chu
I will give you all my love
なぜか優しい気持ちが
For some reason, a gentle feeling
あー いっぱい
Ah, so full
はじめてのチュウ
First kiss
君とチュウ
You and chu
I will give you all my love
涙が出ちゃう男のくせに
Even though I'm a man who sheds tears
be in love with you
Lovin' you
ということで3曲続けて歌っていただきました！
With that, she sang three songs in a row!
ひえー！姫の歌声が沁みるのらねえ
Whoa! The princess's singing voice really touches the heart!
にしても、今日のステージはセットも気合い入ってますなぁ
Even so, today's stage set has so much spirit put into it!
カウントナイトTV、姫のために今年度予算を全部かけて準備いたしました！
CountNight TV prepared this by putting the entire fiscal year's budget for the princess!
ええ！？さあ、さて、お次は一気に7位から4位まで発表です！わくわく！
Eh!? Now then, next up we'll announce ranks 7 to 4 all at once! How exciting!
それでは、みなさんご一緒に！ カウントナイト！
Now everyone, together with us! CountNight!
届け 届け 想いよ 届け
Let it ring, let it ring, take my feelings, let it ring
そうあの日笑顔私の願い全て 君と優しい時間へと
My only wish is for the smile on that day, and all the precious time with you
届け
Let it ring
海の青広がる 赤煉瓦その向こうに
Beyond where the sky meets the waters, past the red bricks
ねえ
Hey
光る磯波超え 雲雀の空眩しい
Crossing sparkling waves, under the dazzling cloudy sky
ああ
Ah
言葉選んで 瞳伏せても
Carefully choosing my words, even looking away
見えない明日も 君の笑顔も！
Even the unseen tomorrow, and your smile!
白く 白く 吹雪のような
White as snow, like a blizzard's breath
そう出逢う前から分かってたこの想い
This feeling I knew long before we met
今ならもっとずっと強く 強く 強く 願いは強く
Now, ever stronger, my wish is stronger
繋ぐよその手を 感じて明日を 信じる優しい未来へと
I'll hold that hand, feel tomorrow, toward a gentle future I believe in
届け
Let it ring
水平線日が落ちて 夕焼け君を染める
The sun dips below the horizon, the sunset dyes you
ねえ
Hey
ずっとこのままなんて いいじゃない想うだけなら
If only this moment could last forever, wouldn't that be fine just to imagine?
けど きっと違うの 行かなきゃだめなの？ 呼吸揃えたら飛沫の中へ！
But surely it's different, do I have to go? Take a breath and dive into the spray!
呼吸揃えたら飛沫の中へ！
When we match our breath, into the spray!
君と君と唄っていたい
I want to keep singing with you, and with you.
戦の日それはきっと全てでなくて
Days of battle aren't surely everything,
帰り道見失わぬよう
so we don't lose our way back home.
聴いて 聴いて その声聴いて
Listen, listen, listen to that voice.
繋いでこの手を 還る明日に
Holding this hand, to the tomorrow we return to,
きっと懐かしいあの場所へ
surely to that nostalgic place.
時の嵐の中で今
Now, amidst the storm of time,
舞い散る花の名前
the name of the dancing, falling flowers,
向かい風 今宵 花吹雪
headwind, tonight, a flurry of flower petals.
積もる 積もる 白雪みたいに
Piling up, piling up, like white snow,
優しく透きとおる時間のような
like a gently transparent time,
きっと きっと 初雪みたいに
surely, surely, like the first snow,
忘れないよ 一瞬を――
I'll never forget that single moment—
深く 深く 深雪のような
Deeply, deeply, like deep snow,
そう始まる前に知っていたこの痛み
this pain I knew before it all began.
今ならもっとずっと深く
Now, even deeper than ever,
強く 強く 想い紡いで
spinning our feelings stronger and stronger.
繋ぐよその手を 感じて明日を
Connecting those hands, feeling tomorrow,
静かな優しい海へきっと届け 届け
surely delivering to a quiet, gentle sea, delivering,
君へと届け 届け
delivering to you, delivering.
男の子と違う 女の子って
Girls are different from boys,
好きと嫌いだけで 普通がないの
with no normal—only love and hate.
でも好きになったら いくつかの
But once I fall in love,
魔法を見せるわ 本当よ
I'll show you several kinds of magic, truly!
そうよ 女の子のハートは
That's right, a girl's heart
星空に 月の小舟浮かべ
floats a small boat of the moon in the starry sky,
夢を探すこともできる
and can even search for dreams.
デリケートに好きして
Make me delicately like you,
デリケートに好きして 好きして 好きして
delicate and like me, like me, like me...
嫌いと感じたら 手遅れみたい
If I feel hate, it seems too late—
サヨナラが心にあふれてしまう
goodbyes overflow in my heart.
興味ない人と 一秒も
We can't spend even a second
一緒にいられない 私達
together with someone we're not interested in.
そうよ 女の子のハートは
That's right, a girl's heart
七色に光る 虹のように
is like a rainbow shining in seven colors,
風が吹くだけでも変わる
changing even with just a breath of wind.
デリケートに好きして
Make me delicately like you,
デリケートに好きして 好きして 好きして 好きして
delicately like you, like you, like you, like you...
そうよ 女の子のハートは
That's right, a girl's heart
星空に 月の小舟浮かべ
floats a small boat of the moon in the starry sky,
夢を探すこともできる
and can even search for dreams.
デリケートに好きして
Love me delicately,
love me delicately.
好きして
Love me,
love me,
好きして
love me.
我愛你 酔いが覚めない
Wo ai ni, I'm so intoxicated.
Oh, I need you 恋が覚めない
Oh, I need you, my love won't fade.
お生憎様の慣れ果て察して
Realize what a sad state you've become.
無問題 破滅してみて
Moumantai, go on and ruin yourself.
Hold me tight トラウマの味
Hold me tight, the taste of trauma.
猛反対 お手お座りでハイ 報酬
Total opposition, sit, give a paw, high reward.
喉の奥がチクンチクン
There's a prickling deep in my throat,
僕はドクンドクン
and my heart goes thump-thump.
鼓動で孤独消してみてよ
Try erasing the loneliness with your heartbeat.
愛も恋も独裁して 僕を独占して
Dictate love and romance, and monopolize me.
このまま中毒になるまでチューしよ
Kiss me until we're addicted just like this.
Get get get on! Get get get on! Get on chu!
熱くときめくくらいに溢れた気持ちが たまらないでしょ
Overflowing with hot, beating feelings, isn't it irresistible?
Get get get on! Get get get on! Get on chu!
Get on! Get on! 我愛你 無問題
Get on! Get on! Wo ai ni, moumantai.
Get Get Get on chu!
ポン・チー・カン 勝負はいつも
Pon-chi-kan, the game is always
トンチンカン 僕に言わせりゃ
Ton-chin-kan, if you ask me.
ちんぷんかんぷんだ 最後はロンでしょ？
It's all gibberish, ending with a ron, right?
もう何回？ 殺られればいい
How many more times? Just let me be killed.
Oh, One night 忘れられない
Oh, one night, unforgettable.
終わんないでトキメキ偏愛 予習
Don't end yet, a preview of pounding obsessive love.
喉の奥がチクンチクン 僕はドクンドクン
A prickling deep in my throat, my heart goes thump-thump.
心ごと引きずり出してみてよ
Try dragging out my very heart.
きもちいいね めんどくさいけど
Feels good, even though it's troublesome,
やっぱ照れくさいけど
and after all, it's embarrassing.
死ぬまで忘れられないチューしよ
Let's kiss until we can't forget it till death.
いかれた街はゾンビで溢れる
This crazy town is overflowing with zombies.
君は僕に恋してる
You are in love with me.
ときめく胸に繋がるロープを引きなよ
Pull the rope connected to my pounding chest.
いくよ Bet bet bet on! Bet bet bet on! Bet on chu!
Here we go! Bet bet bet on! Bet bet bet on! Bet on chu!
Bet bet bet on! Bet bet bet on! Bet on chu!
本気で狂えるくらいの儚さしさが美しいでしょ
Isn't the fragility that drives you truly crazy beautiful?
Get get get on! Get get get on! Get on chu!
せーの ポン・チー・カン 終わんない
Ready, pon-chi-kan, it never ends.
Get Get Get on chu!
ほらね 我愛你 無問題
See? Wo ai ni, moumantai.
Get Get Get on chu!
だんご だんご だんご だんご だんご だんご 大家族
Dango, dango, dango, dango, dango, a big dango family.
やんちゃな焼きだんご やさしいあんだんご
The naughty fried dango, the kind red bean dango,
すこし夢見がちな 月見だんご
the mid-autumn festival dango that dreams a little.
おすましごまだんご 四つ子串だんご
The prim sesame dango, the four-skewer dango.
みんなみんなあわせて 100人家族
Everyone, everyone together, a family of 100.
赤ちゃんだんごはいつも 幸せの中で
The baby dango is always wrapped in happiness.
年寄りだんごは目を 細めてる
The elderly dango narrows its eyes with a smile.
なかよしだんご 手をつなぎ 大きなまるい輪になるよ
The chummy dango hold hands and make a big, round ring
町をつくり だんご星の上 みんなで笑いあうよ
They build a town on the dango planet and everyone laughs together
うさぎもそらで手をふってる でっかいおつきさま
The rabbit waves in the sky at the huge moon
うれしいこと 悲しいことも 全部まるめて
Rounding up everything, both happy and sad things
みんな 今日はみにきてくれて ありがとう！
Everyone, thank you so much for coming today!
いつもルーナイトに家族ってことってコメントされて 違うのなって否定してきたけど
People always comment that Luna Knight is a family, and I've denied it saying that's not it,
今だけは うなたんとルーナイトは家族ってことにしてあげるなら
but if you want to make Unatan and Luna Knight a family just for now,
ルーナイト大好きなのらよ！
I love you Luna Knights so much!
なかよしだんご 手をつなぎ 大きなまるい輪になるよ
The chummy dango hold hands and make a big, round ring
町をつくり だんご星の上 みんなで笑いあうよ
They build a town on the dango planet and everyone laughs together
うさぎもそらで手をふってる でっかいおつきさま
The rabbit waves in the sky at the huge moon
うれしいこと 悲しいことも 全部まるめて
Rounding up everything, both happy and sad things
だんご だんご だんご だんご だんご だんご 大家族
Dango, dango, dango, dango, dango, dango, great family
さて、ランキングも残すところ3位から1位までとなりましたね！
Now, only ranks 3 to 1 are left in the ranking!
何が1位になるんでしょうか？
What could possibly be number 1?
と、その前にスペシャルステージを挟ませてもらうわよ！
And before that, we'll squeeze in a special stage!
え？何それ？
Eh? What's that?
こちらをご覧ください！
Please take a look at this!
なんだ…もう朝か と…
Huh, it's already morning, I thought...
ひとり…ごつ…
Muttering to myself...
焼けたパンにバター ぬり…ぬり…
Butter on toasted bread, spreading it...
やんだ…雨はなんか…しめって…
The rain has stopped, but it's kind of damp...
なま…がわ…き…
Half-dried...
へんな…あし…あと…だと思った…らァ
I thought... "Such weird footprints"...
きのう晩につけた あし…あと…
The footprints I left last evening...
やけに…土が… 水をふくんで
The soil is soaked with water...
なま…がわ…き…
Half-dried...
あァーーーッ
Ahhh!
キンと冷え…ているゥ
It's bitterly cold!
缶カンが
Can can
あァ…なんか冷たくて
Ah, it's so cold
あァ…汗と結露が…混じって
Ah, mixed with sweat and condensation
あァ…靴を…ぬらしている
And making my shoes wet
しめ…て…る…
So damp...
なま…がわ…き…
Half-dried...
ミ・ミ・ミラクル☆ミクルンルン☆
Mi-mi-mirakuru miku run run☆
素直に「好き」と言えないキミも
You who can't honestly say "I love you," either
勇気を出して（Hey Attack!）
Show some courage (Hey Attack!)
恋のまじない ミクルビーム かけてあげるわ
I'll cast the spell of love, the Mikuru Beam, upon you!
未来からやってきたおしゃまなキューピッド
A precocious Cupid who came from the future,
いつもみんなの夢を運ぶの
Always carrying everyone's dreams.
夜はひとり星たちに願いをかける
At night, alone, I make a wish upon the stars
明日もあの人に会えますように
That I can meet him tomorrow, too.
Come On! Let's dance! Come On! Let's dance! Baby!
涙をふいて走り出したら
When I wipe away my tears and start running,
Come On! Let's dance! Come On! Let's dance! Baby!
宙（そら）の彼方へSpecial Generation
Toward the far side of space — Special Generation!
「いつになったら、大人になれるのかなぁ？」
"I wonder when I'll be able to become an adult..."
ミ・ミ・ミラクル☆ミクルンルン☆
Mi-mi-mirakuru miku run run☆
出世の遅いアナタのパパも
Your papa, whose rise to fame is slow, too—
元気を出して（飲みにいこう！）
Cheer up! (Let's go get drinks!)
ふしぎなパワー ミクルビーム かけてあげるわ
I'll cast a mysterious power, the Mikuru Beam, on you!
未来にもあるのかな勇気と希望
I wonder if the future has courage and hope, too.
もしもなかったら少し困るな
If it didn't, I'd be a bit troubled.
あの人もいつの日か私を捨てる
That person will also abandon me someday—
そんなのイヤよ、強く抱いてね
I don't want that! Hold me tight, okay?
Come On! Get chance! Come On! Get chance! Baby!
TOBで株を買い占め
Buy up all the stocks through a TOB!
Come On! Get chance! Come On! Get chance! Baby!
三年越しにMonkey Magic Tonight
Three years in the making, Monkey Magic Tonight!
Come On! Let's dance! Come On! Let's dance! Baby!
涙をふいて走り出したら
When I wipe away my tears and start running,
Come On! Let's dance! Come On! Let's dance! Baby!
宙の彼方へSpecial Generation
Toward the far side of space — Special Generation!
「キスって、どんな味がするんだろう…」
"I wonder what a kiss tastes like..."
恋のマジカルミクルンルン☆ (Ah)
Magical love miku run-run☆ (Ah)
アスファルト タイヤを切りつけながら
While screeching tires against the asphalt,
暗闇走り抜ける
Running through the darkness.
チープなスリルに身をまかせても
Even if I surrender myself to a cheap thrill,
明日ににおびえていたよ
I was frightened of tomorrow.
It's your pain or my pain or somebody's pain
誰かのために生きられるなら
If you can live for someone,
It's your dream or my dream or somebody's dream
何も こわくはない
I'm not scared of anything.
Get wild and tough
ひとりでは 解けない愛のパズルを抱いて
Embracing the love puzzle that can't be solved alone,
Get wild and tough
この街で やさしさに甘えていたくはない
I don't want to lean on kindness in this town.
Get chance and luck
君だけが 守れるものがどこかにあるさ
There is somewhere something only you can protect.
Get chance and luck
ひとりでも 傷ついた夢をとりのどすよ
I'll recover my hurt dream even if I'm alone.
クルマのライトにKissを投げては
Throwing a kiss at car headlights,
車道で踊るあの娘
That girl dancing on the roadway,
冷たい夜空をステージにして
Using the cold night sky as a stage,
悲しくおどけていたね
Acting sadly and playfully.
It's your pain or my pain or somebody's pain
誰かのために愛せるのなら
If you can love for someone,
It's your dream or my dream or somebody's dream
きっと 強くなれる
You can surely become stronger.
Get wild and tough
ひとりでは 消せない痛み心に抱いて
Embracing a pain in your heart that can't be erased alone,
Get wild and tough
この街で 自由をもてあましたくはない
I don't want to toy with freedom in this city.
Get chance and luck
君だけが 守れるものをみつけだしたら
If you find something that only you can protect,
Get chance and luck
ひとりでも 傷ついた夢をとりのどすよ
I'll recover my hurt dream even if I'm alone.
Get wild and tough
ひとりでは 解けない愛のパズルを抱いて
Embracing the love puzzle that can't be solved alone,
Get wild and tough
この街で やさしさに甘えていたくはない
I don't want to lean on kindness in this town.
Get chance and luck
君だけが 守れるものがどこかにあるさ
There is somewhere something only you can protect.
Get chance and luck
ひとりでも 傷ついた夢をとりのどすよ
I'll recover my hurt dream even if I'm alone.
Get wild and tough...
つかもうぜ！ DRAGON BALL
Let's grasp it! DRAGON BALL
世界でいっとー スリルな秘密
The world's most thrilling secret
さがそうぜ！ DRAGON BALL
Let's search for it! DRAGON BALL
世界でいっとー ユカイな奇跡
The world's most joyful miracle
この世はでっかい宝島
This world is one huge treasure island
そうさ今こそアドベンチャー！
Yeah, now is the adventure!
胸ワクワクの愛がGISSIRI
Heart-pounding love, GISSIRI
色とりどりの夢がDOSSARI
Colorful dreams, DOSSARI
この世のどこかで ひかってる
Shining somewhere in this world,
そいつを見つけにゆこうぜBOY
Let's go find it, BOY!
妖怪変化も ぶっとばし
Blowing away any demon or apparition,
雲のマシンで 今日も翔ぶのさ
Today we'll soar on a cloud machine.
Let's try try try 魔訶不思議
Let's try try try, mystical,
空を駆け抜け 山を越え
Fly through the sky and cross the mountains,
Let's fly fly fly 大冒険
Let's fly fly fly, grand adventure,
不思議な旅が始まるぜ
A mysterious journey begins!
手にいれろ！ DRAGON BALL
Get your hands on it! DRAGON BALL
世界でいっとー てごわいチャンス
The world's toughest chance
追いかけろ！ DRAGON BALL
Chase after it! DRAGON BALL
世界でいっとー イカした物語
The world's coolest story
この世はでっかい宝島
This world is a huge treasure island!
そうさ今こそアドベンチャー！
That's right, now is the time for an adventure!
光る雲を突き抜け Fly Away
Piercing the shining clouds, fly away!
からだじゅうに 広がるパノラマ
A panorama spreads all over my body.
顔を蹴られた地球が怒って
The earth, kicked in the face, gets angry
火山を爆発させる
And makes a volcano explode!
溶けた北極の中に
Within the melted Arctic,
恐竜いたら 玉乗り仕込みたいね
If there were dinosaurs, I'd teach them to ride balls!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
何が起きても気分は へのかっぱ
No matter what happens, I feel totally carefree!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
胸がパチパチするほど 騒ぐ元気玉…Sparking!
My heart races so much, the Genki-Dama roars... Sparking!
頭カラッポの方が 夢詰め込める
An empty head can hold more dreams!
笑顔ウルトラZで 今日もアイヤイヤイヤイ……
With an Ultra Z smile, even today is ai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
ハチャメチャが押し寄せて来る
Nonsense comes rushing in,
泣いてる場合じゃない
There's no time to be crying!
ワクワクを100倍にして
Multiplying our excitement a hundred times,
パーティーの主役になろう
Let's become the stars of the party!
夢中になれるモノが いつか君をすげえ奴にするんだ
What you're passionate about will someday make you amazing!
のーてんぴーかん 空は晴れて
Clear sky overhead, no-ten p-kan,
いっぱいおっぱい ボク元気
Lots of energy, I'm feeling great!
トラブルと遊べ ヤンチャ・ボーイ
Play with trouble, you naughty boy!
We gotta power! ドラゴンボールZ
We gotta power! Dragon Ball Z!
のーてんぴーかん 頭さえて
Clear sky, clear head,
らーめんろっぱい ははのんき
Six bowls of ramen, carefree mom!
せいきまつはしゃげ オチャメ・ガール
Celebrate the end of the century, playful girl!
We gotta power! ドラゴンボールZ
We gotta power! Dragon Ball Z!
DAN DAN 心魅かれてく
Bit by bit, you're charming my heart
その眩しい笑顔に
With that dazzling smile.
果てない暗闇から飛び出そう Hold my hand
Let's fly away from this endless darkness! Hold my hand.
君と出会ったとき
When I first met you,
子供の頃大切に想っていた景色を思い出したんだ
I remembered a place that I held dear when I was a child.
僕と踊ってくれないか
Won't you dance with me?
光と影のWinding Road
On a winding road of light and shadow,
今でもあいつに夢中なの?
Even now, are you still lost on him?
少しだけ 振り向きづくなるような時もあるけど
There were times when I wanted to turn back just a little,
愛と勇気と誇りを持って闘うよ
But holding love, courage, and pride, I'll fight on!
DAN DAN 心魅かれてく
Bit by bit, you're charming my heart
Bit by bit, I'm falling under your spell
この宇宙の希望のかけら
Fragments of this universe's hope,
きっと誰もが 永遠を手に入れたい
surely everyone wants to grasp eternity.
ZEN ZEN 気にしないフリしても
Even if I pretend not to care at all,
ほら君に恋してる
look, I'm in love with you.
果てない暗闇から飛び出そう Hold your hand
Let's leap out from the endless darkness, Hold your hand.
ということで、ランキングトップまで聴いてくれてありがとなのらー！
And so, thank you so much for listening all the way to the top of the ranking, nanora!
みんな、これで終わると思った？
Everyone, did you think it ends here?
実は、ラストに重大なお知らせがあるのらー！
Actually, there's a huge announcement at the end, nanora!
ふふ、驚いたと思う？
Hehe, were you surprised?
と、その前にグッズ紹介もあるよー！
And before that, there's also merchandise to introduce!
お待たせ！今年もあるぞ、誕生日記念グッズ！詳細を見てからだ！
Hold on! This year too, there are birthday commemorative goods! Check the details first!
まずはこちら！ルーナのおっぺぇマウスパッド2nd♡ まうおじして第2弾が登場なのだ！
First up is this! Luna's Oppai Mouse Pad 2nd♡ Making its long-awaited second appearance, nanora!
イラストはかんざきひろし描き下ろし！セクシーなうなたんがみんなのお疲れの手を癒してくれるなら！
Illustrated by Kanzaki Hiro! If sexy Unatan heals everyone's tired hands, nanora!
次はこちら！お疲れ様なのらトートバッグ♡ キーホルダーのチェーンを付けられるタイプのトートバッグになってるのら！デザインもかわいいなのだろう、みんないっぱい使ってね！
Next is this! The 'Thank You for Your Hard Work' Tote Bag♡ It's a tote bag where you can attach a keychain! The design is cute too, everyone use it a lot!
一緒にお出かけミニぬいぐるみキーホルダー♡ うなたんがルナイトと抱っこしているデザインになってるのら！これでいつも一緒にならね！
Going Out Together Mini Plush Keychain♡ Designed with Unatan hugging Lunite! This way we can always be together, nanora!
次はこちら！ルーナとルナイトのキラキラピンバッジ♡ ラメやストーンなどが施された豪華仕様のピンバッジセットなのだ！トートバッグにつけてね！
Next is this! Luna & Lunite Sparkling Pin Badge Set♡ A luxurious pin badge set with glitter and stones! Attach them to your tote bag!
ボイス！うなたんはボイスはあまり出さないのだけど、今回は特別に出しちゃうのら！1つ目は「うなたんとイチャイチャデートボイス」！
Voice! Unatan doesn't usually release many voice packs, but this time I'm releasing them specially! The first one is 'Unatan and Flirty Date Voice'!
そして2つ目は「添い寝くんっぽいASMRボイス」！特別ボイスなのでじっくり聞いてなのだろうね！
And the second is 'Sleeping Together-style ASMR Voice'! Since it's a special voice, listen closely, nanora!
そしてフルセット購入特典もあるのら！数量限定バージョンは直筆サインと箔押しメッセージ入りポストカード！
And there's also a full-set purchase bonus! The limited-quantity version is a postcard with a direct signature and foil-stamped message!
今回から数量限定なのでぜひゲットしてなのだろうね！
Since it's limited quantity starting this time, please be sure to get it, nanora!
改めてフルセットはこちらとなります！
Here is the full set again!
フルセット特典として、今年の9月から発売されたホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームで使用できるカードが1枚付くなら！カードはホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップでご購入された方のみ対象となるのだよ！
As a full-set bonus, it comes with 1 card usable in the hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME released this September! The card is only applicable to those who purchased from the hololive production Official Shop!
グッズはこのあとオープンです！みんなよろしくなのだろう！グッズのCM以上でした！スタジオに戻りまーす！
Goods open after this! Everyone please look forward to it! That was the merchandise CM! Heading back to the studio!
はーい、ということで、グッズよろしくなのだろう！そして重大発表！やっと発表するなら！
Hii, so, please check out the merch, nanora! And now, the huge announcement! Finally announcing it!
なんと！オリジナルソング第4弾！タイトルは「守ってルーナイト」を歌うなら！
And! The 4th original song! The title is 'Mamotte Ruunaito', I'm going to sing it!
この生誕配信後にMVの公開と24時に楽曲が配信されるなら！
After this birthday stream, the MV release and midnight song release will happen!
それでは聴いてください。「守ってルーナイト」！
Please listen to it. 'Mamotte Ruunaito'!
聴きなさい。
Listen closely.
汝、この城の扉を叩いた者よ。
Thou who hast knocked upon the doors of this castle.
誓いなさい。このルーナの盾となり矛となり、
Swear! To become Luna's shield and spear,
夜はぐっすり眠れるまでともにいることを！
and to be together until the night when you sleep soundly!
捧げなさい！姫であるぞ！
Offer it! For I am a princess!
ルーナって？
Luna...?
「紅茶のカップかちゃかちゃ鳴らさないってえらい！」
"Not clattering your teacup is a good girl!"
「スコーンだってこぼさず綺麗に食べてすごい！」
"Eating your scone cleanly without dropping crumbs is amazing!"
「たまに王冠どっちが前か間違っちゃうのかわいい！」
"Sometimes getting the crown's front and back mixed up is cute!"
ってよっし！なのはら！開城～！
Right then! Nanohara! Open the gates!
ルーナイト第一条！ 誰よりルーナが好きな人！
Lu-knight Rule 1: Someone who loves Luna most!
ルーナイト第二条！ シルクのお布団持ってきて！
Lu-knight Rule 2: Bring silk duvets!
ルーナイト第三条！ 三時のお茶会来れる人！
Lu-knight Rule 3: Can come to the 3 PM tea party!
守れなかったら即・刺殺！
If you can't protect it, immediate execution!
分かってほしいのら……
I want you to understand...
これも、帝王学を学ぶため……
This is also to study imperial governance...
愛という名の……教育なのら～！
An education... in the name of love!
守ってルーナイト 踊ってくんないと
Escort me, Lu-knight! If you won't dance with me,
プロムナード ボイコットなのはら！
I'll boycott the promenade!
手の甲に忠誠 誓えるの？Chu
Can you swear loyalty on the back of my hand? Chu
ガラスの靴 履かせてワルツ！
Put glass slippers on me and let's waltz!
守ってルーナイト 踊ってくんないと
Escort me, Lu-knight! If you won't dance with me,
ブラウニーにキャンディ どれだけあってもね 君がいなきゃだって！
Brownies and candy, no matter how much, if you're not here!
みんな 心して
Everyone, put your heart into it
捧げなさい！ 姫であるぞ！
and offer it! For I am the princess!
ルーナって？
Luna...?
「お菓子のあと ちゃんと歯磨きするの えらい！」
"Brushing your teeth properly after sweets is a good girl!"
「目覚ましなくたって 起きられちゃうの すごい！」
"Waking up without an alarm clock is amazing!"
「ステップこんがらかったのも かわいい！」
"Getting your steps all tangled up is also cute!"
今日の誉め言葉、よし！なのはら！開城～！
Today's praise: Good job! Nanohara! Open the gates!
ルーナイト第四条！ ルーナを本気にさせる人！
Lu-knight Rule 4: Someone who makes Luna serious!
ルーナイト第五条！ ダイヤの花とか摘んできて！
Lu-knight Rule 5: Pick diamond flowers and bring them!
ルーナイト第六条！ ドラゴンペットに出来る人！
Lu-knight Rule 6: Someone who can make a dragon a pet!
つべこべ言わずに即・実行！
No complaints, immediate execution!
きっと分かってくれるのら……
I'm sure you'll understand...
君主論だって読んだのだ……
I even read The Prince...
恋はいつだって……試練なのら～！
Love is always... a trial!
守ってルーナイト 踊ってくんないと
Escort me, Lu-knight! If you won't dance with me,
オペラハウス 貸し切りなのはら！
I'll rent out the opera house!
誓いの忠誠 約束のChu
Sworn loyalty, a promised Chu
ドレスの裾裳 咲かせてロンド！
Let the hem of my dress bloom into a rondo!
守ってルーナイト 踊ってくんないと
Escort me, Lu-knight! If you won't dance with me,
バルコニー レモンディー 月にシュガー乗せちゃう
Balcony lemon tea, putting sugar on the moon
あの子も綺麗だって そんな たわ言は
"That girl is pretty too"—such nonsense,
おやめなさい！ 姫であるぞ！
stop it right now! For I am the princess!
守ってルーナイト 踊ってくんないと
Escort me, Lu-knight! If you won't dance with me,
プロムナード ボイコットなのはら！
I'll boycott the promenade!
永遠の忠誠 この指にChu
Eternal loyalty, on this finger Chu
ガラスの靴 履かせてワルツ！
Put glass slippers on me and let's waltz!
守ってルーナイト 踊ってくんないと
Escort me, Lu-knight! If you won't dance with me,
ブラウニーにキャンディ どれだけあってもね 君がいなきゃだって！
Brownies and candy, no matter how much, if you're not here!
みんな 心して
Everyone, put your heart into it
捧げなさい！ 姫であるぞ！
and offer it! For I am the princess!